Can't get the monkey off your back?
Then put it in your mouth...
... with Monkeyshine Beer!
Get it, monkey
Get it, get it, monkey
Monkey, monkey
Monkeyshine Beer.
Because it's a jungle out there!
That commercial always
makes me so sad.
But then the guy opens his beer
and girls run at him...
...so everything works out okay.
I meant because the monkey
reminds me of Marcel.
I can see that.
Because they both have those big
brown eyes and the little pouty chin.
And the fact that
they're both monkeys?
I wonder if I did the right thing,
giving him away.
Ross, you had to. He was
humping everything in sight.
My Malibu Barbie will no longer
be wearing white to her wedding.
Remember when he'd borrow your hat...
...and when you got it back,
there'd be monkey raisins in it?
When he did it, it was funny.
When I did it to my boss's hat....
Suddenly, I had this big
"attitude problem."
The One With the Super Bowl, Part 1
Hey, check it out!
Guess what I got?
Rhythm?
No. My first fan mail!
"Dear Dr. Ramoray:
I love you and would do
anything to have you."
My gosh! "Your not-so-secret
admirer, Erika Ford."
Oh, wait.
"P.S. Enclosed, please find
14 of my eyelashes."
In Crazy World, that means
you're married.
It's not addressed to Days Of Our
Lives. This came to your apartment.
She was in our building.
Oh, my God.
I got my very own stalker!
Where are you off to?
There's a paleontology
conference in L.A.
So I figured I'd go and drive down
to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
He will be surprised.
Till he realizes he's a monkey...
...and isn't capable of that emotion.
Phoebe? That really cute guy
is here again.
Okay, so everyone...
... pretend I'm telling you a story
and it's really funny.
So everyone just laugh. Now!
I know, I know!
I'm Rob Donan.
Hi, Rob Donan.
I don't know anything about music,
but I think you're really great.
Anyway, I schedule performers
for children's libraries.
And I was thinking, have you thought
about playing your songs for kids?
I would love to have kids...
...hear me play the songs
that I will write for them.
What do we do for dinner?
We could cook for ourselves.
It's Erika.
My God. The stalker!
Never mind. It's open.
Hitting her with a frying pan
is a good idea.
But we want a backup plan,
just in case she isn't a cartoon!
Let's get out of here!
The one time they're not home!
We'll leave.
When we pass her...
...she won't know me,
because we never met!
That's how radio stars
escape stalkers!
She's coming!
It's me.
This is it.
This is how we're gonna die.
You ready?
Wait, wait, wait!
Erika!
-Mr. Geller?
-Yes, hi.
Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
You had a question?
I can't find the monkey I donated
last year. He's a capuchin...
...answers to the name Marcel?
I'm afraid I have some bad news.
Marcel has passed on.
Oh, my God. What happened?
He got sick,
and then he got sicker...
...and then he got a little better.
But then he died.
I can't believe this!
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller.
But you know, there's an old saying:
"Sometimes monkeys die."
It's not a great saying...
... but it certainly is fitting today.
-Someone should've called me.
-I'm sorry.
Look, I know this can't
bring him back...
... but here, it's just a gesture.
Zoo dollars?
Yes, and come see the bird show
at 4. The macaws wear hats.
It's a lot cuter
if your monkey hasn't just died.
I know.
I can't believe Joey's having
lunch with his stalker!
What is she like?
You remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
Well, she looks
the exact opposite of that.
And she's not crazy?
Oh, no, no.
She's a total whack-job.
She thinks that Joey is
actually Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Oh, my God!
And he's going out with her?
He cannot pursue this.
Just because this woman sees Joey
through the magical box...
...in her living room
doesn't mean she's not a person.
Does she not deserve happiness?
Does she not deserve love?
Why are you looking at me? He's
the one who wants to boff the maniac!
Are you okay?
No. I'm just nervous.
Maybe if I just picture them all
in their underwear....
That's not a good idea. That's
the reason the last guy got fired.
I'm used to playing for grownups.
Grownups drink their coffee
and do their grownup thing.
And kids...
...Iisten.
It's just a huge responsibility.
What?
Are you gonna kiss me?
I was thinking about it.
Alrighty! Let's play some tunes!
-Hi, everybody. I'm Phoebe.
-Hi, Phoebe!
I'm gonna play some songs
about grandparents, okay?
Now Grandma's a person
Who everyone likes
She bought you a train
And a bright shiny bike
But lately she hasn't
Been coming to dinner
And last time you saw her
She looked so much thinner
Now your mom and your dad said
She moved to Peru
But the truth is she died
And someday you will too
-Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
-Yeah, it is.
What?
Well, here we sit, devil-may-care...
...and a while ago you were
reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
That was a tricky one.
In reality...
...that operation takes 10 hours.
But they only showed it for 2 minutes.
Who's "they"?
No one.
Drake, you are so talented.
Let me see those hands.
Oh, these hands,
these beautiful hands.
I could just eat them.
But I won't.
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
No, seriously.
These hands...
...these miracle, magical,
life-giving hands.
Just to be near them, touch them,
maybe even lick one?
All right. Just one.
You're good at that.
Oh, my God! Someone!
He's choking!
Is anyone here a doctor?
Yes, the best doctor in Salem!
Dr. Drake Ramoray!
Meet me in the nocturnal
house in 15 minutes.
Hey, look. I don't really enjoy
being with other men that way.
But, zoo dollars?
It's about your monkey!
It's alive.
I don't understand.
Why didn't you help that man?
Because I'm a neurosurgeon...
...and that was clearly a case of...
... "foodal chokage."
I gotta tell you something
You don't have to tell me anything.
You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
Who am I to question
the great Dr. Drake Ramoray?
I should be happy to be near you.
Hey, l
Hey what?
That's it. Just hey!
Like at the end of a dance. Hey!
There'll be times when you get older
When you'll want to sleep with people
Just to make them like you
But don't!
'Cause...
... that's another thing...
... that you don't wanna do
Everybody!
That's another thing
That you don't wanna do
-Excellent!
-Very informative!
Not at all inappropriate!
Thank you for coming, everybody!
There are cookies in the back.
That was great.
The kids loved you.
Yea! I rock!
And you know why?
Because you told the truth.
Nobody ever tells kids the truth.
You were incredible!
But...?
-How'd you know there was a "but"?
-I sense these things.
It was either "but" or "butter."
The thing is, I think
some of the parents...
...they were hoping that...
...you'd play more songs
about barnyard animals.
I can do that.
Really?
Because that would be fantastic!
What? You wanna kiss me?
I'm thinking about it.
The bat.
Ambassador of darkness.
Flitting out of his cave
like a winged messenger.
Sightless specter of the macabre.
Buddy, my monkey?
Oh, yeah, right.
There was a break-in...
...a few months back.
Inside job.
Your monkey was taken.
The zoo told me
that my monkey was dead!
The zoo!
You believe everything
the zoo tells you?
That's the only thing
the zoo's ever told me.
Of course they'll say that!
They don't want the bad publicity.
It's all a great big cover-up.
Do you have any idea
how high up this thing goes?
That guy Lipson?
Lipson knows?
Lipson knows, huh?
Hello, Mr. Possum.
Enigma of the trees,
upside-down denizen of the night.
-Taunting gravity
-Buddy, my monkey. My monkey?
Word on the street
When I say "street," I mean those
pretend streets here at the zoo.
Of course.
Your monkey found a new career...
...in the entertainment field.
That's all I know.
This is unbelievable!
So what is this information
worth to you, my friend?
Are you trying
to get me to bribe you?
Maybe.
But you already told me everything.
Check it out.
He actually is
the Monkeyshine monkey!
What'll you do?
I'm gonna call the beer company
and try to find him.
That's what I did
when I lost my Clydesdales.
Okay, hi again!
Hi, Phoebe!
Today, we're gonna start with
some songs about barnyard animals.
Oh, the cow in the meadow goes "moo"
Then the farmer hits him
And grinds him up
And that's how we get hamburgers
Now chickens!
Only you who can save her, Drake!
Damn it! I'm a doctor.
I'm not God!
There goes my whole belief system.
It's Erika.
Quick! Shut off the TV.
I wanna see what happens!
I get Leslie out of the coma
then we make out.
How can that be?
You were kissing Sabrina!
Rachel, it's a world
where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
Hey, Erika. Come in.
How did you get here so fast?
I just saw you in Salem.
Right, they choppered me in.
What's up?
You're having a little party too!
-ls she here?
-Who?
Sabrina. I know about you two!
I saw you today, kissing
in the doctor's lounge.
It's not what you think
You told me I was the only one!
All right, look.
That's it.
We shouldn't see each other anymore.
I should have told you
a long time ago...
... but I am not Drake Ramoray.
I'm not even a doctor. I'm an actor.
I just pretend to be a doctor.
Oh, my God! Do the people
at the hospital know?
Somebody wanna help me out here?
Oh, I know! I know!
Where am I?
University Hospital...
... where you've been
for the last 18 years.
How can you be here and there?
Because it's a TV show!
What are you getting at?
I'm not Drake!
That's right!
He's not Drake. He's...
... Hans Ramoray, Drake's evil twin!
Is this true?
Yes! Yes, it is true!
And I know this...
... because he pretended
to be Drake to sleep with me!
And then he told me
he would run away with me!
And he didn't!
And you left the toilet seat up,
you bastard!
Is all this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
You deserve much better than me.
You deserve to be with the real Drake.
He's the one you fell in love with.
Go to Salem. Find him!
He's the guy for you!
Oh, Hans!
Hans?
Hans!
Yo, evil twin!
Right. Goodbye, Erika.
Good luck in Salem.
Take care.
I'll never forget you, Hans.
All right.
The people who threw the water!
Helping you out!
Fired?
Why?
The library board got a lot
of complaints from parents...
...about the stuff in your songs.
I can't believe it!
Did you tell your board that
the kids want to hear the truth?
I see.
Maybe if you just played
some regular kiddy songs?
What do you want me to be?
Like some...
...stupid, big,
like, purple dinosaur?
You don't have to be Barney.
Who's Barney?
I tracked down Marcel and get this.
He's healthy, he's happy...
...and he's in New York filming
Outbreak 2: The Virus Takes Manhattan.
You're kidding!
-This is amazing!
-I know.
I finally get a part on TV,
and the monkey's making movies.
Rachel, I'm ready.
Excuse me. Is this where the
singing lady is, who tells the truth?
I guess that's me.
She's here!
Sometimes men love women
Sometimes men love men
Then there are bisexuals
Though some just say
They're kidding themselves
This is exciting! I haven't
seen my monkey in a year.
What, you never
look down in the shower?
I'm not allowed to make one joke
in the "monkey is penis" genre?
Back up, please.
Back up. Come on.
Excuse me.
Where can we find the monkey?
I'm sorry.
It's a closed set.
I'm sorry, you don't understand.
I'm a friend of his.
We used to live together.
And I have a time share
in the Poconos with Flipper.
There he is!
Hey! Buddy!
Marcel! Marcel!
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
In the jungle
The mighty jungle
The lion sleeps tonight
They won't take you to the vet
You're obviously not
Their favorite pet
Smelly cat
It's not your fault
-What?
-I'm sorry.
What's wrong with that?
You might want to pick
a more masculine note.